前情提要
边  缘  世  界
这里才是我的世界
This here's the only world that I got.
前情提要
边  缘  世  界
这是什么
What is it?
这是最尖端的虚拟现实 弗林 客户让做贝塔测试
Cutting-edge VR, Flynne.Folks want me to beta test it.
你好
Well, hello.
欢迎来到仿真游戏 冰易
Welcome to the Sim, Easy Ice.
准备好了吗
Are you ready?
天哪
Holy shit.
我总是忍不住想 自己真的在那里
I can't help but think that I was actually there.
在某个真的地方
Somewhere that's real.
费舍尔女士 你的处境很危险
Ms. Fisher, you're in grave danger.
情况比你想象的复杂得多
The situation is far more complex than you can possibly imagine.
请立即登录游戏 这很重要
It's crucial that you log back into the sim.
我需要你在接下来几个小时里 忍受巨大的痛苦
I may need you to endure terrible pain in the coming hours.
我保证 这是为了一项崇高的事业
I assure you it's for a very noble cause, all right?
有人在试图联系我
Someone from that company's trying to contact me.
他说有人在暗网上悬赏九百万美元刺杀我们
He says someone put a hit out on us.
这么严重的破坏
A breach of this magnitude
会让我们研究所的所有人都陷于极度危险之中
puts all of us here at the Research Institute in profound peril.
你太让我失望了 丹尼尔
You've disappointed me, Daniel.
我知道 博士
Yes, Doctor.
我们追踪了操作员
We traced the operator.
他所处的位置及时间性 确实让情况复杂化了
His location and temporality complicate the situation, of course.
但我们已采取了必要措施 来消除此威胁
But we've taken the necessary steps to eliminate the threat.
什么措施
Those being?
我们已在一个叫"暗网"的平台上 发了帖 暗网是一个...
We've put up a posting on something called the dark web.
我知道暗网
- It's a... - Yes, I know what it is.
-悬赏任务有人接吗   -几乎立刻有人接单
-Has the offer been accepted? - Almost immediately.
接单的一方可靠吗
By a reliable party?
退伍军人 精锐部队
Ex-military. Elite unit.
我们会为他们提供技术援助
We'll be providing some assistance on the technical side.
我们要杀的不仅仅是他一个
Well, it's not just him that we need dead.
只要跟他有一点关系的 都要做掉
It's anyone even remotely associated with him.
我们在帖子上已经写清楚了 博士
Well, the posting was quite explicit in this regard, ma'am.
焦土策略
Scorched earth.
无人机回航
Drone inbound.
把妈妈带去地下室
Get Mama in the basement.
你能破解吗
Can you hack it?
你们这群喝高的笨蛋坐在火堆旁别动
I need a bunch of dumbass drunks around the fire. Not much motion.
搞定它 里斯 不然我们直接上了
Get it done, Reece, or we go without it.
妈妈
Mama!
无人机传输拦截
启动中
-行了 -把我连上去
Done. Link me.
这些可怜虫 根本不知道他们惹毛了什么人
These sorry motherfuckers have no idea who they just picked a fight with.
连接成功
Linked.
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
神经控制协调协议
激活
无人机传输拦截
完成
搞定
Okay.
长筒枪带了吗
You've got your long guns?
妈妈  醒醒  妈妈 快醒醒
Mama. Mama. Wake up.Mama, wake up right now.
妈妈 醒醒
Mama, wake up!
妈妈 快起来
Mama, get up.
电网关闭确认
无人机锁定
趴下
Stay down!
掩护
Cover!
趴下
Stay down!
趴着
支援
Back up, back up!
无人机锁定
■
确定开始清扫
放哪儿了
Where is it?
拜托 给我进去 快
Fuck. Come on, fucker. Come on.
停下  马上把枪扔了
Stop! Drop your fucking gun now!
-妈妈呢   -她一直在睡觉
- Mama? -It's all right. She slept through the whole thing.
麻烦了 只有十具尸体
Problem.Only seeing ten bodies.
-有一具在房子里 -还是少了两个
- One's in the house. -Counted. Still two missing.
回放
Play it back.
轻机枪部队
LMG team.
他们也把我们给黑了
They hacked us back.
-混蛋 -他们来了
-Motherfucker! -One's on the move!
-弹药不够了 -我也是
- Low on ammo here. - Here, too.
-我不要跑上山 –没人要你去
-Ain't about to be running up that ridge, if that's what you're thinking. -Not asking you to.
伯顿
Burton!
那是谁啊
Who is that?
谁能告诉我发生了什么
Will someone please tell me what the fuck is going on?
你妹妹说我该过来喝杯啤酒
Your little sister said I should stop by for a beer.
不过她没提你们还有这么好玩的派对
She ain't say nothin' about you throwing such a fun party, though.
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
边
缘
世
界
第一季     第2集
艾丽塔
Aelita.
我就知道是你
I thought that was you.
怎么这么巧
What are the chances?
别演戏了 沃尔夫
You're pretending, Wolf.
为什么这么说
Why would you say that?
给你两个选择
You have two choices.
要么告诉我你为什么要追踪我 要么滚蛋
You can tell me the truth, why you've tracked me down,or you can fuck off back up the street.
我认识一个人 他正在查
I know a person who's looking for some information
你当前工作地的信息
about your current place of employment.
研究所吗
The Research Institute?
你认识的这个人是个白痴吧
And this person you know, he's a fool, is he?
据我所知 只有三种可能
As far as I can see,there's three possible categories at play.
白痴 盗窃集团的 或者伦敦警察
Fool. Klept. Maybe the Met...
这位仁兄可不傻
He's not a fool.
那就是盗窃集团的了
So a klept, then.
我为什么要跟这么恶心的世界有瓜葛
Now why would I want to get entangled with such an unpalatable world?
这里面涉及的金钱
There would be a sum of money involved
远远超出你需要的水平
that will carry you far beyond the level of need.
我不想要钱
I don't want money.
你幸福吗 艾丽塔
Are you happy, Aelita?
-以前 每天早晨... -不准你来这一套
-Every morning... - Don't you fucking dare do that.
...我都会问你:"你幸福吗"
...I'd ask you, "Are you happy?"
每次你都会给我同一个答案
And every time, you'd give me the same answer.
尽管当时发生了那一切 尽管我们周围一片荒凉
Despite all that was going on,the desolation all around us.
你还是会说"幸福"
"Yes."
"幸福"
你现在醒来时还是这么想的吗
Do you still wake up like that?
所以这是无私贡献咯
So this is altruism, is it?
当好心人有没有好处费啊
Is there a finder's fee for the Good Samaritan?
利己和利他 两者可以同时存在
Both can exist, can't they?
不是吗
Self-interest and altruism?
我是认真的 你看上去不幸福
I'm quite serious.You really don't seem happy to me.
你认识的这个人 他的这个提案
The individual you know, his overture, or whatever you want to call it,
会让我幸福咯
it's gonna make me happy, is it?
来点神秘气氛 给日子添些色彩
A little bit of intrigue, to liven up your days.
这有什么不好
Where's the harm in that?
喂
Hello?
天哪 你听上去很累嘛
Good God, Wilf,you sound like hell.
已连接
列夫·祖博夫
应该是你打电话的时间不对 列夫
The hour may have something to do with that, Lev.
那你就应该知道这事很紧急
Which should give a sense of the urgency at play.
出什么事了
What's going on?
我派了车过来 就等在楼下
I've sent a car. It's waiting downstairs.
现在凌晨5点 我哪儿也不去
It's 5:00 in the fucking morning.I'm not going anywhere.
我付你佣金的
I pay you a retainer,
如果我没弄错的话 金额还不小
quite a generous one if I'm not mistaken.
远高于市价 因为毕竟这个职务只是...
Given what I understand to be the going rate for...
你是怎么称呼自己的来着 威尔弗 "调停者"
what is it you call yourself again, Wilf? A "fixer"?
我很喜欢这个简单直接的称呼
I do admire the brute simplicity of the title.
我只是在要求你做本职工作而已
All I'm asking is that you do your job.
帮我解决一个麻烦 现在就去
Fix a problem of mine,and fix it now.
有人想接那个赏金任务 刺杀那女孩和她家人
The bounty on the girl and her family, someone tried to claim it.
更确切地说是一个团队
Or to be more precise, a team of someones.
而且十分暴力
And rather violently.
我们运气好 但我们不会一直走运
We got lucky,but our good fortune isn't likely to last.
所以我们的技术人员给那个女孩做了边缘
So my technicals have built the girl a Peripheral.
我要你让她登入边缘 马上去做
I need you to get her inside it now.
有了她 我们就很有可能找到艾丽塔
She's our best chance of finding Aelita.
艾什 我能感觉到你不赞同的眼神
I can sense your glare of disapproval, Ash.
怎么了
What is it now?
你的朋友内瑟顿先生
Your friend, Mr. Netherton.
我担心你们的私人关系可能影响了你的判断力
I worry your personal attachment might be affecting your judgment.
他不是执行这项任务的合适人选
That he's not the right man for the job.
为什么
Because...?
他属于你会雇来帮你跑腿的那种人
He's the sort you pay to carry a bag of money to someone,isn't he?
狡猾、易被遗忘
Slippery. Unmemorable.
是当局会忽视的那种人 因为他不像你
The type authorities overlook because he's not like you.
-他不是... –不是讲究生活的富翁
-He's not a... -A wealthy bon vivant?
不是杰出的俄罗斯血统的后裔
A descendant of an illustrious Russian bloodline?
不是艺术的赞助者
A patron to the arts?
他不是个杀手
A killer.
他只是个贴心听话的宠物
He's just a pet.Obliging and sweet.
而目前的情况可能需要我们多一点...
And the current situation may require us to be a little bit more...
凶残
Brutal?
改天我会告诉你 我是怎么认识威尔弗的
One day I'll share with you how I first met Wilf.
他不喜欢谈论那件事 他很谦虚
He doesn't like to talk about it.Quite modest, really.
但这么说吧 谈到他施暴的能力
But let's just say,when it comes to his capacity for violence,
绝对符合我们家族的标准
he is one of the family.
尤其在有适当的动力驱使时
Especially when properly motivated.
没有谁比威尔弗·内瑟顿
And no one could possibly be more motivated to find Aelita
更有找到艾丽塔的动力了
than Wilf Netherton.
抱歉 弗林
I'm sorry, Flynne.
我知道这是你最不想做的
I know this is the last thing you want to do,
但我们需要情报
but we need the intel.
如果你想修改外表
If you'd like it altered in any way,
我们可以轻松满足你
we can easily accommodate you.
我叫威尔弗·内瑟顿
I'm Wilf Netherton.
我就直接点 因为我们没有时间谈别的
I'll be as direct as possible,since neither of us has time for anything else.
我一直在找一位名叫艾丽塔·韦斯特的女性
I'm trying to find a woman.Aelita West.
你可能是最后一个见到她的人
If I'm not mistaken,you might be the last person to have seen her.
艾丽塔·韦斯特
我想你应该先告诉我
You see, I'm thinking you should probably tell me
艾丽塔·韦斯特
为什么有人来杀我和我家人
why people are trying to come and kill me and my family first.
艾丽塔·韦斯特
然后我可能会跟你玩这个关于失踪女性的仿真游戏
And then, maybe I'll go and play your stupid missing-lady sim.
这里不是仿真游戏
You aren't playing a sim, Ms. Fisher.
你在"边缘"的化身之中
You're inside what we call a Peripheral.
远程临场
Telepresent.
就像使用自己身体那样操纵化身 所有这一切...
Piloting that body as if it were your own.And all this, it...
我带你逛逛
Let me show you.
这里不是伦敦
This ain't London.
为什么这么说
Why would you say that?
人都到哪去了
Where are all the people?
这个解释起来就有点困难了
Well, that's where things begin to get a bit tricky.
这里确实是伦敦
This is London.
但是70年以后的伦敦
But London 70 years from what you think of as the present.
你指望我会相信你的鬼话
I'm sorry, you really just expect me to swallow that?
我是穿越了吗
That I've time traveled here?
-穿越到了未来的伦敦   -不是
-To future London? -No.
完全不是
Not at all.
假设是你说的时间旅行
If it were time travel, as you say,
你会真的身处伦敦
you'd be here physically.
而现在只是数据传输
This is merely a matter of data transfer.
技术术语叫量子隧穿
Quantum tunneling is the technical term for it.
-我知道你很困惑 -我没有
-I understand your confusion. -No, I'm not confused
一点也不困惑 我只是不相信你
at all, actually.I just don't believe you.
你想要我真诚的证明吗
You'd like my bona fides?
你的母亲
Your mother.
她罹患脑瘤
She has a brain tumor.
神经胶质瘤
A glioma.
这也不用穿越到未来才知道吧
Okay. You don't really need to be from the future to know that one.
你母亲会在四个星期内去世
It's going to kill her in four weeks.
9月22日
On September the 22nd.
深夜
Late in the evening.
瞎说
That's not true.
医生说这病不会威胁生命 她后面的日子还长着
Doctor told her it won't do her in.They said there's plenty of stuff in line ahead of that.
她的疼痛有没有加剧
Has her pain been intensifying?
这是第一个征兆
That's usually the first sign.
讣告
■
艾拉·费舍尔
于9月22日深夜去世
享年50岁...
我们开发了一种治疗神经胶质瘤的药物 十分有效
We've developed a drug to treat gliomas.Rather easily.
对我们来说小菜一碟
It's like spraying a weed, more or less.
我已经把制剂发到你的药房 他们正在打印
I've sent the formula to your pharmacy.They're printing it now.
我们买不起乔恩药房的药
We can't afford Pharma Jon.
我们已经把钱汇给药房了
We wired payment direct to the pharmacy.
可以考虑一下 费舍尔女士 不过要快
Think on it, Ms. Fisher. But with alacrity.
情况紧急 我一再强调了
The situation is urgent. I can't stress that enough.
你和你家人仍处在极度危险之中
You and your family... You remain in grave danger.
会有源源不断的人来追杀你们
Those men who came to kill you,they won't be the last.
你需要我来帮忙阻止他们
You need my help to stop them.
我也需要你的帮助
And I'll need yours in turn.
回头见
I'll see you soon.
大家有的说埋了 有的说烧了
Burying and burning have both come up for discussion.
还有的说走法律通道 联系治安官办公室
Along with the straight and narrow approach of contacting the sheriff's office.
我认为得听听你的意思 然后再决定
I thought we should hear from you before we committed ourselves.
埋了 我到城里去
Bury them.I'm headed into town.
-去干什么   -回来再告诉你
-What for? -Tell you when I get back.
-不能一个人去 -好吧
- You can't go alone. - Fine.
派个人陪我
Then send somebody.
乔      恩      药      房
你有事要告诉我吗 妈妈
You want to tell me something, Mama?
告诉你什么
About what?
神经胶质瘤
About your glioma?
噢 亲爱的
Oh, sweetie.
谁告诉你的
Who told you?
对不起 弗林
I'm sorry, Flynne.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
他们告诉你这些...
They tell you something like that...
妈妈
Mama...
听起来很傻 但你会突然之间意识到每一天都很宝贵
It sounds silly.But suddenly, you realize how precious each day is.
想到会让你伤心痛苦 哪怕只有一秒钟
And the idea of stealing even one second from you,of...
我也于心不忍
of weighing you down with sadness,
所以我就决定不告诉你...
when I could protect you?
你还有多少时间
How long?
六个星期
Six weeks...
如果我走运的话
...if I'm lucky.
我告诉护士如果我走运 就根本不会走到这一步
I told the nurse, if I was lucky,I wouldn't be here in the first place, would I?
这种新药 是...
This new drug, it's...
实验性的
It's experimental.
不知道里面是什么成分
We don't know what's in it.
最坏又能坏到哪去呢 弗林
What's the worst it could do, Flynne?
让我早点去了
Kill me a little quicker?
没事的
Come on.
好吧
Okay.
怎么回事
Fucking A.
-嘿 -嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
桌子上有咖啡
Coffee is on the desk.
谢谢
Thanks.
我现在真的需要一些情报
I could really use some intel right about now,
你知道些什么吗
if you got it.
你不会相信我的
You're not gonna believe me.
说说看
Try me.
这不是仿真游戏
It ain't a sim.
当我带上设备时 我在操控一个真实的身体
When I put on the headset, I'm operating an actual body.
我猜是一种机器人
It's some kind of robot, I guess,
但是比机器人更真实
but a whole lot more realistic than that.
外貌像我 感觉也像我
It looks like me.Feels like me.
只是它在伦敦
Except it's, uh, in London.
那个人是这么说的
This guy says.
我能信
I can believe that.
这还不是最离奇的
Well, that ain't the hard part yet.
他说我在那里时目睹了一些东西
He says I witnessed something while I was there.
所以那些人要来杀我灭口
Something that these folks are wanting to kill me to keep quiet.
这些有什么难信的
I still don't see what's so hard to believe.
那是在未来 伯顿
It's in the future, Burton.
他来自未来
Where he is.
2100年
2100.
他肯定给出了一些理由 所以你才相信
I assume he gave you a reason to believe that?
你上楼时去看妈妈了吗
You check on Mama on your way up?
她好吗
Is she okay?
她说自己很好
Claims she's fine.
不过莱昂说她的生命体征不太正常 好像在跟什么搏斗
But Leon says her vitals are out of whack.Like she's fighting something.
怎么了
Why?
那个人给了我一样给妈妈用的东西
This guy, he-he gave me something for her.
治疗她肿瘤的药物
A drug.For her tumor.
他说会治好妈妈
He says it will cure her.
去他的 可不能轻信他的鬼话...
Well, fuck that, 'cause we're not taking his word on anything.
我已经给她用了
I gave it to her.
什么
You what?
他给我看了妈妈的讣告
He showed me her obituary, okay?
-弗林 你不能... -如果什么都不做的话
- Flynne, you can't - just give her... - She's gonna die in four weeks
-她最多只能活四周 -这你都能信
-if we don't do nothing about it. -And you just believed that?
这是真的 伯顿 感觉很真实
It was real, Burton. It felt real.
感觉真实
Felt real?
你这是疯了吗
Flynne, are you out of your fucking mind?
我会上线 收集更多信息
I'll go back. I'll get more intel, if that's what you want.
没门儿
No fucking way.
-我要上线 -不行 他没说让你上
- I'm going in there. - No.He doesn't want you.
-他需要的是我 -我才不管他要谁
-Okay? He wants me. -I don't give a fuck who he wants.
你这是在让他觉得他能发号施令
That's part of the problem. You're letting him think he's in charge.
你干嘛一直要乱来 把事情搞得一塌糊涂
Goddamn it, Burton. Why do you have to go and fuck things up all the time, huh?
对不起 好吗
Fuck. Look, I'm sorry.Okay?
这里需要你
We need you here.
这你知道
You know that.
万一来追杀我们的人越来越多怎么办
What happens when more people come hunting us down?
但我要去 伯顿
But I'm going, Burton.
这事没得商量 明白吗
This ain't a discussion.Okay?
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
我们在哪
Where are we?
诺丁山 一座屋子的后花园
The rear garden of a house in Notting Hill.
房主是列夫·祖博夫
It belongs to Lev Zubov.
那个就是他 穿马甲的
That's him, in the waistcoat.
那是...
Are those...?
袋狼类动物 不过你们可能有其它叫法
Thylacine analogs.Though I believe you might call them something else.
塔斯马尼亚虎
Tasmanian tigers.
我在电视上见过 但里面说它们已经灭绝了
I saw them on a show once,but they said that they were extinct.
重现这些动物也是列夫的一个爱好
Well, one of Lev's hobbies is recreating such things.
通过DNA
From their DNA.
它们会咬人吗
Do they bite?
这两只是作为家庭宠物研发的
These two are designed for domestic companionship.
另有一个平行种系 被养育成适合野生生存
There's a rival genetic line, bred to be feral.
我们来这干什么
So, why are we here?
我们来诺丁山是为了跟列夫和他的两个技术员见面
We're in Notting Hill to meet with Lev and his two technicals.
在我们开始前 让你在他的庭院适应一下
More specifically, we're in his garden to give you a moment to acclimate before we begin.
开始什么
Begin what?
给你介绍一下情况
Debriefing you.
是列夫雇我寻找艾丽塔的
Lev is the man who hired me to find Aelita.
她失踪了
The woman who went missing.
技术员是什么
And what's a technical?
在技术方面有专业知识的人
Someone with expertise in, ah... technical matters?
他很会说嘛
Gift for words, hasn't he?
树边上气势汹汹的那位男士叫奥西恩
Ossian is the gentleman looming rather threateningly against the tree.
他在技术上面很有一套 你以后就会知道
He has a knack for that sort of thing,as you'll soon see.
桌子旁边一脸阴沉的年轻女子叫艾什
And Ash is the exceedingly gloomy-looking young woman at the table.
他们负责两个世界之间的连接
They work to maintain the connection between our two worlds.
这种连接不如我们希望的坚固
Which is apparently rather more tenuous than one might prefer.
能不能让他们进来 免得他说出些不合适的话
Can we bring them in before he says something we can't unsay?
午饭做好了 威尔弗
Lunch is served, Wilf.
你可以把音乐关了
You can shut it down.
如果我没有上线 这个躯壳会怎么样
What happens to this thing when I'm not in it?
它有八小时的睡眠周期
It has an eight-hour sleep cycle.
其余时间 如果你在自己的时间桩 它会由人工智能操控
The rest of the time,when you're off in your stub, it runs on AI.
我的时间桩
My "stub"?
如果现在的一方与过去某个时间接触
When a party from our present made contact with the past,
那这个过去的时间会立即分支 形成自己的连续体
that past immediately branched off and formed its own continuum.
你可以把它叫做平行时间线 也就是时间桩
Or parallel timeline, if you will.Or stub.
换句话说
In other words,
我们两条时间线是完全一样的 直到我们进行接触
our two timelines were identical until that moment of contact.
两条时间线才会岔开
At that point, they separated.
-你根本没讲清楚 -你可以随时纠正我
-You're not helping at all. -Any moment you'd like to jump in.
这概念十分烧脑 我们有时也头痛
It can all be rather confusing, even for us.
或许我们应该先说最紧急的事情
Perhaps we should stick to the most urgent matters at hand,
然后你渐渐会明白一些次要细节
and trust that the secondary details will fall into place.
紧急的事   比如说有人来刺杀我和我家人
Urgent, like the people coming to kill me and my family?
这算一个例子
For instance.
或者从我们的角度来说 指的是艾丽塔·韦斯特怎么了
Or, from our perspective,urgent being what happened to Aelita West.
为什么她对你们这么重要
Why is she so important to y'all?
艾丽塔在一家名叫"研究所"的企业工作
Aelita worked for an entity called the Research Institute.
因为职务关系她可以访问你的时间桩
Her duties there gave her access to your stub.
我们付钱给她 让她提供一个进入时间桩的暗门
We've been paying her to provide us with a trapdoor into it.
她现在失踪了 我们很可能失去这个连接
Now that she's missing, we risk losing that connection.
你们去我的世界干什么呢
Well, what were you all up to in my world, then?
没懂你意思
I'm sorry?
你们费了老大劲来调查
Seems like you're going to an awful lot of trouble here to find things out.
我很想知道为什么
Kind of just begs the question: Why?
-可以管它叫求知欲 -就像游戏一样
-You could call it intellectual curiosity. -Like a game?
像在玩仿真游戏一样
Like you're playing a sim?
我觉得可以这么类比
I suppose that analogy could be made.
所以你们觉得我们不是真实的 我 还有我的家人和朋友
So, we aren't real to y'all? Are we? Me, my family,my friends.
那你觉得我们是真实的吗
Are we real to you?
我暂时还不确定
I'm working on it.
有人来了
Got a visitor.
汤米·康斯坦丁
Tommy Constantine.
徒步 离这里500米
On foot.Half a klick up the road.
把无人机开回来 你撤回来 我过去
Bring the drones in. Pull back. I'm coming up.
收到
Roger that.
卡洛斯 你来替我
Carlos, I need you to cover for me.
我来了
On my way.
-要我干什么   -就坐着 保持警戒
- What do I do? - Just sit and watch.
如果她醒了 别告诉她我去哪儿了
If she wakes, don't tell her where I've got to.
-我不会撒谎 -没让你撒谎
-I ain't gonna lie to her, Burton. -I'm not asking you to.
告诉她我去巡视外围了 就让她呆在那儿
Just tell her I'm walking the perimeter.And then try your best to keep her there.
你给我妈的那个药
That drug you gave my mother,
我妈注射之后病得更重了
all it's gone and done is make her sicker.
药物会见效的 我保证 再过一段时间
It will accomplish what I promised, I assure you.Give it time.
她没有多少时间了
Which is the one thing she don't have, ain't it?
你们自己说的 你们怎么知道我妈妈的事呢
According to y'all? How'd you all get that information, anyway?
你们还知道什么  你们有她的讣告
What else do you all have? You got her obituary.
那么我会怎么样
But... what happens to me?
就像我们之前说的 如果我们世界的人接触了...
Well, as we explained before,when someone from our world made contact with yours,your timeline...
我懂 就是时间桩呗
Yeah, I get it. That's the whole stub thing.
但你们时间线里的弗林·费舍尔 怎么样了
But what happened to the Flynne Fisher in your timeline?
她结婚了吗  有孩子吗
I mean, does she get married, or have any kids?
她还活着吗
Or is she still alive?
我的哥哥怎么样了
What about my brother?
在某个时间点之前有记录
There's information to a certain point.
但之后 记录就变得不一致
But after that point, the records become rather spotty.
哪个时间点  为什么
What point? Why?
70年里会发生很多事 费舍尔女士
A lot can happen in 70 years, Ms. Fisher.
也确实发生了很多事情
-A lot did happen. -Yeah,
具体是什么事
but what? Specifically.
感觉我们有点偏题了
I fear we're getting a little off track here.
你们有什么在瞒着我
What are you all hiding from me?
这些问题都很好 到时候会答复你的
These are all excellent questions, and in time, they'll all be answered.
相信我
I give you my word.
你老是这么说 但好像没什么意义
Yeah, you keep on saying that,but it's just starting to sound like it don't mean that much.
-费舍尔女士... -我妈妈什么时候才能好起来
-Ms. Fisher... -When will my mother get better?
他们互相交流的时候 可以对声音加密
They can encrypt their voices when they address each other.
你会习惯的
You'll grow accustomed to it.
不过你还是会有火气
Although, I'm afraid the irritation never quite dissipates.
我只是在告知艾什
I was simply informing Ash
那个药的有效率是57%
that the medication in question has a 57% efficacy rate.
什么意思
Which means?
达到预期结果的能力
The ability to produce a desired or intended result.
这个词汇来自拉丁文"efficācia"
Borrowed from Latin "efficacia."
我知道这个词什么意思
I know what the fucking word means.
我妈妈的病到底能不能好
What does it mean for my mother?
我们不能确保药物一定有用
We can't guarantee that the drug will work.
看来"小菜一碟"在未来世界的意思跟我那个年代的不一样
Well, I'm guessing "spraying a weed" means something pretty different in the future, huh?
你们能把灭绝的动物复活
Y'all got extinct animals you've brought back to life,
时间旅行 会动的纹身
time travel, moving tattoos...
帮助一个最近运气不佳的好女人
Seems like it shouldn't be too hard to help a good woman
应该不会太难吧
who's had a shitty run of luck lately.
先把她治好
Make that happen...
然后我会跟你们聊那个失踪的小姐
...and I'll start talking about your missing lady.
我也向你保证
Give you my word on it, too.
你看到过这种东西吗
You ever come across anything like this?
这是枚6.8毫米特种用途弹
You know what? That's a 6.8 SPC.
以前打仗时 我们有时会用它们
We used those in the war on occasion.
你觉得是凶狠的大毒枭
Builder muscle, you think?
说得通
Good a guess as any.
一路赶来这儿
All the way out here, though?
这似乎有点奇怪 不是吗
That seem a bit odd, don't it?
汤米 整件事情本身就很奇怪
Whole damn thing seems pretty odd to me, Tommy.
你和弗林没有生我和迪迪的气吧
Hey, you and Flynne ain't mad at Dee Dee and me, are you?
为什么要生气
Why would we be mad?
这里停着这么多车
All them vehicles.
感觉你们已经准备好办烧烤派对了
Looks like y'all getting ready to roast a pig or something.
我在想 为什么没有邀请我们呢
Just, uh, wondering why we didn't get an invite.
这是里斯的卡车吧
That's Reece's truck there, right?
莱昂  卡洛斯也在
And Leon? Carlos, too?
我们在搞一次愚蠢的无人机飞行比赛
Yeah, just one of our stupid drone tournaments.
你没蠢到会跟我们一起玩那个吧
I didn't figure you'd be fool enough to mess around with those.
应该没有
No.Suppose not.
弗林
Flynne.
伯顿
Burton.
见鬼
Fuck.
我知道你在这件事上投入了多少个人精力 威尔弗
I know how personally invested you are here, Wilf.
所以我担心你急着去引导费舍尔小姐
So I worry that you might feel an understandable instinct
这也是可以理解的
to push the pace a little with Ms. Fisher.
但我们不该在她适应之前给她施加太多压力
I think we should let her find her feet before we pressure her too much.
你说我们不能浪费时间
You said time was a resource we can't afford to waste.
如果花时间是为了
And I wouldn't consider it wasted
让她更加听话 那就不算是浪费
if it were time spent making her more...tractable.
当初我以为你只是想跟艾丽塔谈谈
My understanding was that you simply wanted to speak with Aelita.
所以我才会同意安排你们认识
It's the only reason I agreed to arrange an introduction.
确实 正是那些谈话
Indeed.And those conversations
让我们进入了这位年轻女性的世界
led to the possibility of access to this young woman's world.
你为什么想进入
Why did you want access?
威尔弗
Wilf.
我一直觉得你是那种天生能够识别
You've always struck me as someone with a gift for discerning the difference
什么该知道 什么不该知道的人
between good knowledge and bad knowledge.
该知道的事会给你带来力量或优势
Good being that which brings you power or advantage.
不该知道的事 可能会将你置入致命的危险之中
Bad being the type which might put you in mortal peril.
我不会对朋友撒谎 这是我很自豪的一点
It's a point of pride. I don't lie to my friends.
所以请你注意一下 别瞎问问题
So, please, take some care of what you ask.
我可不想把你当外人
I'd hate to stop thinking of you as a friend.
向弗林和你妈妈问好
Make sure to say hi to Flynne and your mama for me.
我会的 汤米
Yeah, I'll do that, Tommy.
他说什么了
What did he say?
有两辆越野车被遗弃在路上
Two abandoned SUVs up the road a ways.
使用了新型隐形技术
With some new kind of cloaking tech.Which answers that question.
你还好吧
You okay?
我不知道 伯顿
I don't fucking know, Burton.
这一切怎么会发生的
I mean, how the fuck is all this happening right now?
后面有一大堆尸体
There's a pile of dead bodies back there.
你不能这样想
You can't think like that.
那些未来世界的朋友会帮我们吗   还是我们只能靠自己
Your buddies from the future gonna help us any? Or we on our own?
他们说还在观察中
They said they're watching.
我猜他们会在下一波袭击之前 给我们发警告
I guess they'll try to give us a warning before the next wave hits.
-怎么样的警告   -能做到多少是多少
-How much of a warning? -Much as they can manage.
他们说在给我们汇钱
They said they're sending money, though.
很大一笔钱 二十五万美元
A lot.$250,000.
如果钱打到我账户 我就没有社保了
Soon as that hits my account,I'm gonna lose my social security.
我知道 别担心 我跟他们说了 会想别的办法
Yeah, I know. Don't worry, I told them.They said they're gonna figure out a workaround.
什么办法
Which is?
天哪 我的老天爷
Holy shit. Holy fucking shit.
我中彩票了
I just won the goddamn lottery!
我一直都很走运 你们俩都知道
I've always been lucky. You both know that, don't you?
这件事跟运气没关系 莱昂
Luck ain't got nothing to do with it, Leon.
-你们俩在那儿遇到的几个人... -声音轻点
-What? You two meet some folks in the futur... - Indoor voice, Leon.
未来世界  他们帮我中奖   这件事除了运气 还能怎么解释
The future? They help me win the lottery? How else you gonna explain that but luck?
莱昂
Leon.
皮克特先生送的 恭喜你中奖
From Mr. Pickett. With his congratulations.
科贝尔·皮克特  真的
Corbell Pickett? For real?
没错
Yep.
我的老天
Jesus fuckin' Christ.
举起酒杯 点头表示谢意
Just raise your glass.Nod your thanks.
注意礼貌 弗林
Manners, Flynne.
我要...上洗手间
I... I just got to... Got to use the bathroom.
那该死的混蛋还在盯着我们看
Fucking asshole's still looking at us.
我们的白痴堂弟确实中奖了
Well, our idiot cousin did just win the lottery.
所以别人有所关注也很正常
So makes us kind of interesting for a minute or two.
现在相信我说的未来世界的事了吧
So, you believe me now? 'Bout this whole future thing?
我承认 相信了一点
Step closer, I'll admit.
相信了不少
Not a small one, either.
这是什么
What's that?
我们的武器采购清单
Shopping list for our little army.
轮值表
Duty roster.
康纳在哪里
Where's Conner at?
你知道康纳这个人
You know Conner.
我知道 我还知道找他帮忙或许能算是做一件好事
I do.I also know that maybe asking him to help us might count as a good deed.
或许  也或许会害我们被一锅端
Might. Might also get us all killed.
得了 伯顿
Come on, Burton.
他那天晚上可帮了大忙
He came in pretty damn handy the other night.
我们那是运气好 而且幸好康纳来的时候没喝高
We spun the dial, and thankfully, Conner came up sober.
我猜 也许除了莱昂堂弟之外 运气好的人还不少
Which I guess means cousin Leon is not the only one with a bit of luck on his side.
你想说什么
What's up? You got something you want to say?
我已经说过了
Already said it.
弗林 我没法修复已经无法补救的东西
I can't go fixing something that's unfixable, Flynne.
尤其是现在这种情况下
Not in the middle of all this.
好吧 我要回家了
All right, then, I'm gonna head home.
等等
Wait, wait, wait. Hold up.
我跟里斯谈了那个仿真游戏
I talked to Reece about that sim.
你带大家从谷仓突围
How you got us all out of the barn.
然后呢
And?
你把羊群赶出去 因为你同情它们
And you let the sheep out 'cause you felt bad for them, right?
它们出去之后 拖拉机就出现了
And then, once they were gone, the tractor was revealed.
就好像仿真游戏为你的同理心
So it was like the sim gave you...
发了奖励
...an empathy bonus?
但是从战术上讲 这样做可能让我们损失宝贵的资产
But tactically, that would've been sacrificing a valuable asset.
那些纳粹士兵准备袭击我们 羊群是我们唯一的掩护
Those Nazis were about to storm us, and the sheep were the only cover we had.
行啊
Okay.
-那你会怎么找到拖拉机呢   -我就是这意思
-How would you have found it then? -That's my point.
你同情康纳 我知道 我们也为他难过
You feel bad for Conner.I get it. We all do.
但这次不会有人为同理心发奖励
But nobody's handing out any empathy bonuses here, Flynne.
在现实世界里 不会有人给我们"拖拉机"
In the real world, there ain't gonna be no fucking tractor.
当然 但如果有拖拉机
Sure.But if there were one...
你也找不到 不是吗
...you wouldn't have found it.Now would you?
家里见
I'll see you at home.
该死的 弗林
Damn it, Flynne.
...康乃尔大学 昆虫学系
...of Entomology at Cornell University.
...蜂群中的蜜蜂
needs of the colony.
有工蜂、雄蜂、蜂王
Workers, the drones, the queen,
他们都为蜂巢的健康运行作出贡献
they all contribute to the healthy functioning of the hive.
每只蜜蜂 包括蜂王在内
And none of them, not even the queen herself,
都无法在缺少同伴支持的情况下独自存活
can survive without the support of the others.
然而 虽然他们具有协作精神 并且高度组织化
However, despite their cooperative and highly regimented society,
环境的压力还是让蜜蜂的数量锐减
environmental pressures have placed the population of bees into freefall,
从而导致我们社会发生
which has led to a cascade of agricultural deficiencies
一连串的农业缺陷和经济动荡 比如...
and economic turmoil in our own society.For instance,
一项针对加利福尼亚杏仁种植户的调查
a study conducted in California with almond farmers
显示因缺少蜜蜂 他们每年产量减少7万5千...
found that the absence of bees decreased their annual income by $75,000...
有没有担心过 自己会用那玩意向别人射击
You ever worry you might shoot someone with that thing?
比如醒来时吓了一跳
Wake up startled-like?
你就因为这个不太过来玩了
That why you don't come and visit so much no more?
你害怕我拔枪比你快
Afraid I might beat you to the draw?
你喝醉了 康纳
You drunk, Conner?
我可不赖
I'm something.
这是肯定的
That's for sure.
你没有回答我的问题
You didn't answer my question, though.
你为什么不来玩了
Why don't you come a-visiting?
我这不是来了吗
I'm a-visiting now, ain't I?
我没来是因为害怕哪天会发现你死在了家里
Got so I figured I was gonna find you dead one of these days.
我不知道自己是否能承受
Didn't know if I could live with that.
那为什么现在又来了
So why are you here now?
那天晚上枪战之后 你就走了
You disappeared on us, after our night of mayhem.
因为好玩的部分过去了
The fun seemed to die down pretty quick.
我不太会过太平日子
I've learned I'm not so good with the quiet periods.
事情在持续发酵
We got an ongoing situation.
我需要一个优秀的上士
I could use a decent staff sergeant.
那天晚上 在我去你家的路上
The other night, when I was headed toward your place?
那些人听到我来
Those boys, they heard me coming,
都藏到树丛里
hustled into the brush.
我只看到其中一个 他的枪口对准了我
I only saw one of them, but he had me scoped.
他只要扣动扳机就可以结果我 但你猜他怎么着
All he had to do was twitch a finger.Know what he did?
他直接放我过去了
Just let me roll by.
我猜他们是去贝克那儿
I figured they was headed to the Baker place,
贾斯珀不知怎么背叛了科贝尔·皮克特
that Jasper crossed Corbell Pickett somehow, and...
我在路上的时候
I kept thinking on it...
一直在想
...as I was going up the road.
那个人放我一马只有一个原因
There's only one reason I could guess why that boy would let me by.
他在可怜我
It's pity.
我越想越生气
More I thought on that, the madder I got.
我决定要杀了那个人 不管他去哪儿
I mean, I decided I was gonna kill that boy, no matter where he was headed.
等我调头找到他时
By the time I got back,
你们被那些家伙围困住了
those fellas had your balls in a nice tight grip.
我觉得作为邻居 不好意思不帮忙
Only seemed neighborly to ease the pressure.
接下来的半天时间里 我感觉很好
Felt pretty good for about 12 hours or so.
就好像补偿了自己似的
Almost like I'd made things right for myself.
你估计退伍军人管理局花了多少钱
How much money you reckon the VA spends,
让我们这些受伤的人重新振作
trying to put all us Humpty Dumpties back together again?
远远不够
Less than it would take.
其实他们大可让我们互相射击
Turns out they could just let us all start shooting each other.
整个问题就解决了
Solve the whole damn problem,don't you think?
一半人会死 还有一半会开心
Half of us'd be dead,the rest would be happy.
别告诉我交火没有让你开心
Tell me that firefight didn't make you happy, Burton.
就是了
There it is.
就是这样的
There it most definitely fucking is,
我没说错吧
am I right? Am I right?
你那里是什么情况
What you got going on out there?
弗林去了未来的伦敦 看到了一些不该看的
Flynne took a trip to future London. Saw something she wasn't supposed to.
如今未来世界的人在雇人追杀我们
Now people from there are hiring folks to kill us.
我是醉了 但还没醉到会信这些鬼话
I'm pretty fucked up, but not that fucked up.
我没让你相信我 我是需要帮助 醒醒酒
I didn't say you had to believe me.You just need to help. Sober up.
去我们那里驻扎
Come camp at our place.
莱昂可以协助 如果你需要
Leon's there for an offload, if you want it.
这再也不是他的工作了
It's not his job no more.
我觉得他从没把这个当成工作 康纳
I don't guess he ever saw it as a job, Conner.
如果他听到你这么说 可不会很开心哦
Probably wouldn't be too happy to hear you describe it that way, either.
我刚刚说过 我会宰了那个可怜我的小子
I just told you I killed some boys for pitying me.
-然后   -你跟他一样
- And? - You doing the same thing?
我这是同理心
I was trying for empathy, actually.
区别在哪里
What's the fucking difference?
我也说不清楚
Fucked if I know, man.
总之这是我们的邀请 来不来看你
Look, the offer is there if you want it.
但你必须保持清醒 这没得商量
But the sober part is nonnegotiable.
我现在说的话你明早还会记得吗
You gonna remember me standing here,telling you all this, come morning?
我得说...
I'd say...
百分之五十概率吧
...it's fifty-fifty.
音乐选择
黄金雨-卡梅伦·伊恩·迈克布莱德
今晚夫人没来吗  先生
¿No esposa esta noche, Señor?
老婆不在 过来轻松一下 曼努埃尔
Flying free this evening, Manuel.
也许你需要一个伴侣
Perhaps you'd like una compañera?
你这老滑头
Why, you old devil.
你把我当什么了
What do you take me for?
您是一个充满激情的人  不是吗
Un hombre de gran pasión,¿no?
你要这么说的话
Well, put it like that? I...
我不会拒绝有人陪伴
Guess I wouldn't spurn some company.
你叫什么名字 亲爱的
And what is your name, honey?
卡门
Carmen.
跟香蕉女郎同名
Like the Chiquita lady?
她是谁
¿Qué es eso?
以前有种水果叫香蕉
Used to be a fruit called the banana.
被某种真菌杀死了 太可惜了
Killed off in some sort of fungus.Terrible shame.
你有什么才艺吗
You, uh...have any talents I should be aware of?
能让我们单独聊聊吗 小姐
Would you excuse us, señorita?
嘿
Hey.
要联系到你可真难啊 皮克特先生
You're quite a difficult man to contact, Mr. Pickett.
我们的记录显示 在2030年左右
Our records indicate that you are an individual
你是克兰顿颇有权势和影响力的人物
with some power and influence in Clanton,circa 2030.
而且看起来 你这个人做事不会有什么忌惮
And it also seems that you're a man who doesn't indulge in too many scruples.
我说对了吗
Is that correct?
现在这是什么情况
What the fuck is going on here?
我们有点事 需要了解当地情况的人才能完成
We have a situation that would appear to require some local knowledge.
我们愿意付你一千万美元
We'd like to pay you ten million dollars
想请你做掉社区里的两个人
to eliminate two members of your community.
你是谁  国土安全部的
Who are you? Homeland Security?
你们这些混蛋黑到这里来了
You fuckers hacked this thing?
我们已准备好现在就把25%的钱转到你账户
We're prepared to transfer 25% into your account now,
这就算是定金吧
as a good faith payment.
尾款在完事之后付清
The rest will be paid upon completion.
这两个人的名字是 弗林·费舍尔和伯顿·费舍尔
The individuals' names in question are Flynne and Burton Fisher.
你以为我是傻子
You think I'm a fool?
这是圈套
This is entrapment, asshole.
这也太明显了
Open and shut.
结束游戏
End game!
我的天
Jesus Christ.
这帮白痴
Fucking idiots.
米拉格罗斯·科尔迪龙
"米拉格罗斯·科尔迪龙"的搜索结果
"米拉格罗斯"是什么意思 - 给宝宝取名
威尔弗·内瑟顿
没有"威尔弗·内瑟顿"的进一步的匹配结果
艾丽塔·韦斯特
"艾丽塔·韦斯特"的搜索结果
哈瓦那好玩吗
How was Havana?
当然是你在的时候比较好玩
Always better when you're there.
我不信
Oh, I doubt that.
我敢打赌 你一个人时会招惹各种麻烦
Bet you get up to all sorts of trouble on your own.
跳跳恰恰舞
Some cha-cha-chá?
恐怕我们可能要暂时对古巴说再见了
I'm afraid we might need to take a break from the old Tropicana.
为什么
How come?
账户存入
科贝尔
Corbell?
伯顿 上来 马上
Burton, get up here right now.
妈妈
Mama?
你在干什么  你没事吧
What are you doing? You okay?
我很饿 我...
I was hungry.
我以为是在做梦
I thought I was in a dream.
妈妈
Mama.
我看得见啦 弗林
I can see, Flynne.
-妈妈 -我能看见你了
-Mama. -I can see you.
我能看见你了
I can see you.
下集预告
边  缘  世  界
你和一个叫科贝尔·皮克特的人有什么关系
What connection do you have to a man named Corbell Pickett?
如果你不能时不时地
Now, you won't get anywhere in life
鼓起勇气残忍一回 你这一生不会有大出息
if you don't have the courage to be cruel now and then.
他才是冷血的人 我们不是
That's the kind of person that he is.That ain't who we are.
应该有更简单的办法来结果这个女孩
There ought to be a simpler way to kill a girl.
艾丽塔留下了一个或许能找到她的线索
Aelita left a clue as to her potential whereabouts.
她总是很喜欢猜谜
She was always fond of riddles.
威尔弗 这是我家的房子
Wilf...that's my house.
我到了
I've arrived.